(Howard:)that ladies pretend
they don't do
(Howard:)even though they do?
(Sheldon:)You know...
which yogurt I mean.
(Howard:)I didn't touch it.
Must have been Stuart.
(sighs)
Maybe Raj is right.
(Bernadette:)Maybe it's time we tell him
he needs to move out.
(Howard:)We should have done
it months ago.
(Bernadette:)I know, but his store
was reopening,
(Bernadette:)and then there were the
holidays, and then he was sick.
(groans)
Yeah, right.
(Howard:)Sick. He didn't have jaundice.
(Howard:)He just looks like that.
(Emily:)All right.
Tonight's the night.
(Howard:)Agreed.
(Howard:)When he gets home, I'm
dropping the hammer.
(Bernadette:)Ooh, I like
when you take charge.
(Howard:)Oh, I'm not taking charge--
you're the hammer.
(Stuart:)So...
(Leonard:)why haven't we
picked a date?
(Penny:)You know why.
(Leonard:)Well, of course I know why.